Guide to the Allison Davis Papers 1932-1984
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence
  - University of Chicago, Department of Education, Francis S. Chase, manuscripts, memoranda, 1955-1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago, Department of Education, John T. Wilson, manuscripts, memoranda, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago, Office of the Dean, Division of the Social Sciences, manuscripts, memoranda, questionnaire, 1949-1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago, Office of the Dean, Division of the Social Sciences, faculty reports, 1951-1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago, Office of the Dean, Division of the Social Sciences, Judson Hixson, "1973 Pre-Freshman Summer Program: Final Report," manuscript, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago, Office of the Dean of Students, housing, memoranda, pamphlet, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago, Office of the President, Committee on African and Afro-American Studies, correspondence, manuscript, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago, Office of the President, Committee on University Policy for Black Students or Harris-Davis Committee, manuscripts, memoranda, minutes, reprints, charts, notes, clippings, 1961-1973 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  - University of Chicago, Office of the President, Committee on University Policy for Black Students or Harris-Davis Committee, Society for the Promotion of Lobbying in the Interest of Black Students, memoranda, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - University of Chicago, Office of the President, Edward H. Levi, memoranda, clipping, 1968-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - University of Chicago, Office of the President, John T. Wilson, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - University of Illinois, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - University of Maryland, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - University of Rochester, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - University of Wisconsin, 1964, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - V, general, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - W, general, 1946-1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Warner, W. Lloyd, eulogy, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Wayne State University, 1961-1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Wisconsin State University, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Woodlawn Community Board, memoranda, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Woodlawn Community Board, James F. Redmond, "Woodlawn Experimental Schools Project," manuscript, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - X-Z, general, 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified, 1946-1968 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Series III: Student Career
  Notes, notebooks, and papers collected and written by Allison Davis as part of his graduate work in Anthropology from 1932 until 1942 are included in Series III. Davis enjoyed a rich and varied student career, studying at Harvard, the London School of Economics, and the University of Chicago. However, it is not always readily apparent at which institution or in what context a given paper was written or notebook compiled. Dates have been provided where available.
  - Bibliographies, syllabii, ca. 1937-1940 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Anthropology 228, "Final Examination," 1940 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Anthropology 325, North American Archaeology, notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Anthropology 326, Archaeology and Physical Anthropology, notes, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
  - Anthropology 326, Comparative Institutions, W. Lloyd Warner, bound course notebook, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Anthropology 326, Comparative Institutions, inserts from pp. 112-113, note cards, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Anthropology 326, "Relation of Physical Anthropology to Archaeology," student paper, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Anthropology 353, Maya, Aztec, and Related Indian Cultures, Robert Redfield, bound course notebook, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Anthropology 353, inserts from pp. 84-85, 136-137, notes, charts, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Anthropology 353, "Cultural Relations between the Ancient Civilizations of the Maya, the Valley, and Peripheral Areas," student paper, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Anthropology 353, "Spanish and Indian Elements in Contemporary Zapotecan Culture," student paper, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Anthropology 363, "A Criticism of Sex and Temperament in Three Primitive Societies," student paper, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Africa, bound course notebook, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Africa, inserts from pp. 60-61, 144-145, notes, charts, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ethnology, Fred Eggan, notes, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Family, W. Lloyd Warner, notes via Dorothy O. Anderson, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Method in Cultural Anthropology, Robert Redfield, notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Nature of a Theoretical Natural Science of Society, A. R. Radcliffe-Brown, seminar notes, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Physical Anthropology, bound course notebook, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Physical Anthropology, inserts from pp. 22-23, 150-151, notes, charts, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Practical Phonetics, notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Primitive Society, outlines, notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
  - "Acculturation of Minority Groups in American Urban Areas," student paper, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "Communal Composition of Songs in South and Southeast Africa with Remarks upon the Ritual Status of Songs," student paper, ca. 1932 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "Is There an Historical Relationship Between Lacustrian and West African Cultures?" student paper, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - "Proposal of Subject for a Thesis to be Submitted in Partial Fulfillment of the Requirements for the Degree of Doctor of Philosophy in Anthropology," manuscripts, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - "Song in South and Southeast Africa with Observations upon the Dance in the Same Area," student paper, annotated bibliography, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - "A Survey of the Data Relating to the Economic Status, Social Biology, and Sociology of the American Negro, 1930," manuscript, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - "Witchcraft, Rain-Making, and Divination in South Africa," student paper, annotated bibliography, ca. 1932 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Series IV: Course Materials
  Series IV has been divided into four subseries: (1) Course Work, (2) M.A. Abstracts and Proposals, (3) Ph.D. Abstracts and Proposals, and (4) M.A. Theses. The first, Course Work, primarily concerns lectures, transcripts and notes from those courses taught by Allison Davis at the University of Chicago. This material dates from the late 1950s through the early 1970s, and focuses on Davis's work on ego development and maintenance. It is worth noting that Davis used the classroom as a proving ground for his own writing, and that one is apt to find striking similarities between his lectures and his more formal writings of the same period.
  The remaining three subseries, M.A. Abstracts and Proposals, Ph.D. Abstracts and Proposals, and M.A. Theses, are all materials gathered together by Allison Davis and range from 1942 to 1978. Files are arranged alphabetically by candidate.
  - Subseries 1: Course Work
    - General, bibliographic notebooks, inserts, undated (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
    - General, bibliographies, syllabus, notes, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - General, Child Development Abstracts, bibliographic notes, ca. 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - General, Master's Comprehensive Examinations, memoranda, 1962-1966 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - General, Committee on Human Development, Department of Education, workshops, outlines, memoranda, bibliography, notes, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - General, Modern Community, outline, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - General, Social Evolutionism, notes, ca. 1935 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - General, Social Orientation of the Child, outline, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - General, Social Psychology, notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - General, "The School in the Social Order," outline, memoranda, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Education 201, 301, 302, 317 Charles E. Bidwell, W. Lloyd Warner, 321, 358, 536, Human Development 421, 422, Sociology 330 W. Lloyd Warner, Carson McGuire, bibliographies, syllabii, examinations, 1942-1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Education 208, student paper, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Education 301, student papers, 1948-1950 (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
    - Educational Psychology 490, student paper, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Sociology 213, student paper, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Sociology 213, miscellaneous, student papers, 1952-1965 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
    - Education 304 A, lectures, partial manuscripts, notes, 1955-1966 (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
    - Education 304 A, bibliographies, syllabii, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Education 304 A, examinations, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Education 304 A, interview data, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Education 304 A, Master's Comprehensive Examinations, 1954-1959 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Education 304 A, student papers, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Education 304 A, Eleanor E. Maccoby, et al., "Child-Rearing Practices," manuscript, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Education 308 Y, notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Education 308 Y, bibliographies, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Education 308 Y, curriculum units, student papers, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Education 308 Y, examinations, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Education 308 Y, interview data, case study sketches, analytic devices, childrens' stories, written responses, correspondence, notes, 1953-1957 (Box 16, Folder 18-19)
    - Education 308 Y, Master's Comprehensive Examinations, 1954-1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Education 308 Y, student papers, outlines, 1952-1961 (Box 17, Folder 2-5)
    - Education 308 Y, "Ability and Survival," "Culture and Intelligence," manuscript, summary, partial manuscripts, notes, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Education 308 Y, "Personality and Social Mobility," manuscript, notes, ca. 1956 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Education 308 Y, Otis D. Duncan, "Is the Intelligence of the General Population Declining?" reprint, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Education 308 Y, Jacob W. Getzels, Kenneth J. Rehage, and Herbert A. Thelen, "Elementary Teacher Training Program," outline, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Education 308 Y, Ernest A. Haggard, "Techniques for the Development of Unbiased Tests," reprint, notes, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Education 308 Y, H. H. Remmers and Benjamin Shimberg, "SRA Youth ," reprint, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Education 310, Master's Comprehensive and Ph.D. Preliminary Examinations, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Education 311, lectures, outline, notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Education 311, bibliographies, syllabii, 1952-1954 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Education 311, examinations, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Education 311, interview data, questionnaire, notes, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Education 311, Master's Comprehensive Examinations, 1954-1957 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Education 311, student papers, 1954-1956 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Education 311, Sigmund Freud, "Formulations Regarding the Two Principles in Mental Functioning," "Negation," manuscripts, ca. 1951 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Education 311, Alan Grey and Benjamin Brody, "Relationships Between Social Background and Psychological Characteristics of Psychiatric Patients," manuscript, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Education 312 A, 312 G Havighurst, outline, bibliography, syllabus, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Education 312 A, Master's Comprehensive Examination, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Education 320, lectures, transcripts, notes, 1966-1974 (Box 18, Folder 13-18)
    - Education 320, lectures, 1966-1974 (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
    - Education 320, lectures, Chester, Emma, and Marge, undated (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
    - Education 320, lectures, Dora and Hans, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
    - Education 320, bibliographies, syllabii, memoranda, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Education 320, examinations, 1963-1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Education 320, Master's Comprehensive Examinations, 1962-1967 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Education 320, slips of the tongue, manuscripts, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Education 320, student outlines, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Education 320, student papers, 1964-1975 (Box 20, Folder 2-5)
    - Education 320, "Achievement During Adolescence and Adulthood," with Robert D. Hess, manuscripts, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Education 320, "Adolescent Psychology," manuscript, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Education 320, "Developmental Relationships Between the Parental Family and the New Family," manuscript, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Education 320, "The Educability of the Children of the Poor," manuscript, notes, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Education 320, "Identity in Adolescence and Young Adulthood," Leo Franklin Lecture, Wayne State University, manuscript, notes, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Education 320, "Independence and Identity," manuscript, news release, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Education 320, "Plan for Two Books Dealing with Social and Psychological Processes in the Development of the Ego During Adolescence and Young Adulthood," manuscript, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Education 320, Irene Josselyn, "The Ego in Adolescence," "Psychotherapy of Adolescents at the Level of Private Practice," reprints, notes, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Education 320, University of Chicago, "Study of Teacher Trainees' Attitudes towards Significant Others," manuscript, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Education 320, Benjamin Wright, "How to Use the Tatso Questionnaire," "Identification and Becoming a Teacher," "Identification Origins of the Self in Young Women," "Love and Mastery in the Child's Image of the Teacher," "The Relation Between Identification and Psychic Structure," "Teacher's Self-Awareness and Their Evaluation of Childhood Authority Figures," manuscripts, questionnaire, memoranda, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Education 320, unidentified, "Indications for Psychoanalysis," in The Psychoanalytic Treatment of Children, partial reprint, ca. 1945 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Education 320, reprints, 1955-1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Education 336, lecture notes, correspondence, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Education 336, bibliographies, ca. 1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Education 336, examinations, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Education 336, Master's Comprehensive Examinations, 1961-1967 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Education 336, student papers, 1963-1965 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Education 336, student-teacher profiles, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Education 336, Anna Freud and Dorothy Burlingham, "Infants Without Families," notes, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Education 336, Ernest A. Haggard, "Social-Status and Intelligence," reprint, notes, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Education 336, reprints, 1945-1966 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Education 346, lecture notes, syllabii, memoranda, 1965-1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Education 346, bibliographies, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Education 346, examinations, 1961-1972 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Education 346, Master's Comprehensive Examinations, 1960-1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Education 346, student papers, 1965-1971 (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
    - Education 346, student-teacher profiles, ca. 1960 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Education 346, "Diversity in the Curriculum," Mobilization for Youth Curriculum Center, lecture, notes, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Education 346, "Teaching Language and Reading to Disadvantaged Negro Children," manuscript, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Education 346, Rebecca C. Barr, "A Study of the Process Involved in Learning to Read," student paper, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Education 346, Chicago CORE, "Testimony of the Chicago CORE at the 1961 School Budget Hearing," transcript, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Education 346, Robert J. Havighurst, "Metropolitan Development and the Educational System," manuscript, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Education 346, Robert D. Hess, "Educability and Rehabilitation," manuscript, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Education 346, William J. Hicklin, Henry M. Reitan, and Harold F. Rahmlow, manuscript, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Education 346, Jerry Hirsch, "Individual Differences in Behavior and Their Genetic Basis," reprint, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Education 346, Susan B. Silverman, "Compensatory Education for Cultural Deprivation," reprint, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Education 479, lecture notes, bibliographies, examinations, student paper, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Sociology 354, lecture notes, bibliography, examinations, clipping, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Sociology 354, student papers, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Sociology 354, Raymond Prince, "Western Psychiatry and the Yoruba," manuscript, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2: M.A. Abstracts and Proposals
    - Jenks, Lucille, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Jordan, Daniel C., 1960 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Malter, Richard F., 1964 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Miller, David L., 1960 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Moore, Lucy, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Polsky, Harold, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Strangman, Eugene H., 1964 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Tobin, Sheldon, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Trojan, David J., 1960 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 3: Ph.D. Abstracts and Proposals
    - Abato, Yvonne, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Ahmad Kamal, A. F. M. H., 1962 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Alford, Harold J., 1964 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Al-Hamash, Khalil Ibrahim, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Allem, C. Dean, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Altbach, Philip G., 1964 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Anthony, Bobbie M., 1965 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Barbarik, Paul, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Bashshur, Munir A., undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Bebout, James E., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Beck, Hugo E., undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Ben-Zeev, Sandra, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Berlin, Barney, amendations, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Borth, Audrey M., undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Bowman, Thomas R., 1962 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Bradford, Clarence, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Brottman, Marvin A., undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Carnes, Alice, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Cernius, Vytas, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Chekouras, Sister Mary Irenaeus (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Choppin, Bruce H. L., 1966 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Chow, Yung-teh, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Chung, Bom Mo, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Collard, Roberta, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Collier, Juanita, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Collins, Orvis, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Courtney, Brother Leonard, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Crotty, William, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Curtis, Conrad, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Dave, R. H., undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - DeBoer, Peter P., 1966 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Dockrell, William B., 1962 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Eells, Kenneth, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Epstein, Erwin H., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Eubanks, John, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Fattahipour-Fard, Ahmad, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Feldvebel, Alexander M., undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Fielder, Marie, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Finder, Morris, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Finn, Jeremy D., 1967 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Freund, Lucy D., 1963 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Gilbert, Edward H., undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Goble, Eva L., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Goldblatt, Phyllis, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Goldiamond, Betty, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Green, Dorothy, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Griffin, Sister Mary Georgita, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Haddad, Fuad S., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Haddad, Safia S., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Hall, Cleo, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Handel, Gerald, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Heaton, Ada B., undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Heinze, Shirley, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Hendricks, Floyd W., undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Heslep, Robert D., 1963 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Hess, Robert D., 1950 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Hink, Douglas L., 1963 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Hoock, William C., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Horton, Aimee I., ca. 1962 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Hull, Ethel I., 1969 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Jackson, John D., 1962 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Jernberg, Ann, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Jewell, Robert W., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Kaiser, Gertrude E., 1964 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Kelly, Sam P., 1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Klever, Gerald L., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Kornacker, Mildred, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Kraines, Ruth J., 1962 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Kratzmann, Arthur, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Lalor, Ida B., undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Lane, Ray U., undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Larmee, Roy A., undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Larmer, Nancy, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - LaVigne, Lorraine, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Lee, Robert E., 1963 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Lerner, Barbara A., 1963 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Levit, Leonore, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Lupton, Daniel E., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Lyell, Ruth G., 1962 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Manske, Armin A., 1942 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Matz, Milton, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Mendelson, Lloyd J., undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Mitchell, James V., Jr., reprint, notes, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Murray, Walter I., undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Nawas, Munir, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Netherton, James D., undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Noël, Edward W., undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Noll, James W., undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - O'Brien, Harriet, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Ohlson, Virginia M., undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Okpala, Charles E. N., undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Oppenheim, Alan, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - O'Shea, David, undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Patton, June O., 1974 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Peizer, Sheldon, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Pelligrini, Francis E., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Peterson, Donald E., 1960 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Peterson, Harry, undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Pitruzello, Philip, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Pittman, Davis, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Powers, Thomas E., 1964 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Queeley, Mary A., 1963 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Reed, James C., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Reinke, Ralph L., undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Rezler, Agnes G., undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Rich, Robert M., 1964 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Robbins, Melvyn, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Saxe, Richard W., undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Sayegh, Wahbah A., undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Scott, Ralph, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Shakelle, Richard B., 1962 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Sherman, Barbara, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Shulman, Lee S., 1963 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Sizemore, Barbara A., undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Edward B., undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Robert E., undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Stone, Douglas E., undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Thompson, Sister Mary St. George, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Tobin, Sheldon S., 1963 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Trexel, Emogene, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Tyroler, Robert L., 1963 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Walberg, Herbert J., 1963 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Wayson, William W., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Weeres, Joseph G., 1971 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Weiss, Joel, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Werner, Norma, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - White, Irving S., 1962 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - White, Verna, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)